propertyobserver.com.au 2015-09-22

# Privacy

The website, www.PropertyObserver.com.au and the Property Observer email alert are wholly owned by the Property Observer media group. This privacy policy relates directly to the Property Observer website and email alert. 

**Privacy Policy Purpose**

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to advise subscribers, customers, staff members and those applying for positions with Property Observer about what kind of information the organisation may collect, how that information may be used, to whom it may be disclosed, how that information is stored (including security of the information), the processes for correcting information held and the disposal of such information by Property Observer.

**Use and Disclosure of Personal Information**

Property Observer will use personal information provided to it only for the purpose for which it was provided. Personal information will not be used for any other purpose without the consent of its provider unless Property Observer is required by law to disclose that information. Property Observer may be required to disclose personal information to third parties in order to provide a service requested. Property Observer will not disclose personal information provided, such as name, address, email address or telephone number, to any organisation or person outside Property Observer unless the provider has authorised Property Observer to do so.

**No Sale of Personal Information**

Property Observer will not sell or receive payment for licensing or disclosing personal information. From time to time Property Observer readers may be invited to respond to surveys which may be conducted by a third-party organisation, in such cases no personal information will be disclosed by Property Observer to the survey company.

**Access and Correction**

Property Observer will provide, where possible, access for providers of personal information to their file. Providers may correct any information that is incorrect and instruct Property Observer to delete the information from its files. Those who have reason to believe information held is inaccurate should inform Property Observer by contacting Property Observer through the contact links published on the Property Observer website and email newsletter:

Reasonable steps will be taken to correct the information so that it is accurate, complete and up to date.

**Security**

Property Observer uses reasonable administrative, technical, personnel, and physical measures to safeguard personally identifiable information in its possession against loss, theft, and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. No data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure. Remember to close your browser when you have finished a user session. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet café. You as an individual are responsible for the security of and access to your own computer.

**Complaints About Privacy**

Queries regarding privacy complaints and disputes should be addressed through the contact links published on the Property Observer website and email newsletter.

Property Observer will investigate all complaints.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Property Observer is continually monitoring privacy developments and accordingly, from time to time may modify this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in the law, self-regulatory initiatives and/or technology. Amendments to the Property Observer Privacy Policy will be posted on [www.propertyobserver.com.au](http://www.propertyobserver.com.au/).
